{
    "subject": "resource/Guyana",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Guyanese_dollar",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Guyana is the Guyanese dollar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9866206645965576,
            "question": "Is the Guyanese dollar the official currency of Guyana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9355891942977905,
            "question": "What is the currency of Guyana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9061168432235718,
            "question": "What is the name of the currency used in Guyana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8891076445579529,
            "question": "Are there any other currencies used in Guyana besides the Guyanese dollar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8765299320220947,
            "question": "Can you buy goods and services with the Guyanese dollar in Guyana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7468727827072144,
            "question": "What is the symbol for the Guyanese dollar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7438055276870728,
            "question": "If you were traveling to Guyana, what currency would you need?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7043886184692383,
            "question": "What is the exchange rate of the Guyanese dollar to the US dollar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6648131012916565,
            "question": "How has the value of the Guyanese dollar changed over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5233502388000488,
            "question": "How do you pronounce 'Guyanese dollar'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Guyana is the Guyanese dollar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8785_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the value of the Guyanese dollar changed over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8785_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the exchange rate of the Guyanese dollar to the US dollar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8785_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were traveling to Guyana, what currency would you need?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8785_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8785_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8785_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8785_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8785_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8785_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8785_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8785_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8785_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8785_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8785_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple \"The currency of Guyana is the Guyanese dollar\" is supported by the documents. \n\nHere is the JSON response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"The currency of Guyana is the Guyanese Dollar\" and provide additional details about it, such as its symbol ($), subdivision into cents, and management by the Bank of Guyana."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}